Guide to the Paul Hibbert Clyde and Mary (Kestler) Clyde Papers, 1924-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Unprocessed additions, (5 boxes and 5 folders)
  - Acc. 99/354, 1985-2001, (2 boxes)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1998 (Box 1, Acc. 99/354)
    - Asian Perspectives: Journal of Archaeology for Asia and South Pacific, Fall 2001 (40:2) (Box 1, Acc. 99/354)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Acc. 99/354)
    - Clyde, Mary Kestler. Flashbacks to Dawn (Box 2, Acc. 99/354)
    - Watercolor of East Duke Building (Box 2, Acc. 99/354)
    - Various color and black and white photographs (Box 2, Acc. 99/354)
  - Acc. 11/196
    Includes autographed portrait of Admiral Togo, Paul Clyde's diplomas from Stanford, and various greeting cards, printed materials, and miscellaneous photographs.
    - Framed autographed portrait of Admiral Togo (Box 1, Acc. 11/196)
    - Letter of transmittal from Paul Clyde to Pace Clyde, 1976 (Box 1, Acc. 11/196)
    - Information folder, 2011 (Box 2, Acc. 11/196)
    - Printed materials, 1941-1991 (Box 2, Acc. 11/196)
    - Operating Reserve directory, 1968 (Box 2, Acc. 11/196)
    - Photographs, 1914-1984 (Box 2, Acc. 11/196)
    - Stanford diplomas and tassels, 1920-1925 (Box 2, Acc. 11/196)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 2, Acc. 11/196)